borderlinx.com 2013-06-26

# Borderlinx | Privacy policy

## New Terms and conditions as of August 2011 governing use of this website and Borderlinx services

We know that the privacy of your personal information is important to you. We respect your privacy and are committed to maintaining the confidentiality and security of any personal data which we receive from you and retain on your behalf.

We are committed to responsible data management and comply with applicable data protection legislation. We apply industry best practices to protect the security of the data stored on our systems. We will collect, store and use your personal information only to support and enhance your relationship with us, for example, to process and ship your packages, provide service and support, answer your questions, and communicate news to you about our service and our shopping partners' products and services. We will not sell your personal information to anyone. We will not disclose your personal information to anyone outside the Borderlinx organisation, except as necessary to our trusted partners and suppliers to enable Borderlinx to provide services to you.

You can browse the non-interactive parts of our website without giving us any personal information, although automated information is conveyed about your computer or mobile device and the pages on our site you visit. If you don't agree with our Privacy Policy, you should not create an account or use the Borderlinx interactive services.

You may contact **Customer Service** if you have any questions or concerns about the privacy of data you give us.

## Who we are

In this Privacy Policy, references to 'Borderlinx' 'we' and 'us' are to Borderlinx Europe SA, 475 avenue Louise, 1050 Brussels, Belgium.

## The information we collect and how it is used

We may collect information from you via this website or by e-mail, telephone, live chat sessions, or alternate electronic or paper communication.

  * ### Information collected

Any personal details you submit, such as name, address(es), telephone numbers, e-mail address, etc. are used only to enable us and our suppliers to provide service to you, for example: to create and maintain your Borderlinx account; to process your orders for Borderlinx services; for receiving, storing, processing and shipping your packages; and for communicating with you. All information you supply will be treated in a confidential manner. Your computer system information including type and IP address (your computer's individual identification on the Internet) may be automatically logged by our web server.
  * ### Cookies

Cookies are small bits of information stored on your own computer and are used to enhance your interactive experience on the Borderlinx website. Our use of cookies allows us to retain the state of your web session and also to personalize and enhance your experience on our website. In registering with Borderlinx and by using Borderlinx's service, you consent to our use of cookies. You can, if you wish, remove, control, manage or block cookies on your machine by following instructions in your web browser's Help menu; however, if you block all cookies, it may adversely affect your interaction with our website.
  * ### Web beacons

We may use web beacons on our site or in our e-mails. A web beacon is an electronic image which is used to recognize a cookie on your computer when you view a web page or e-mail. Web beacons help us measure the effectiveness of our site in various ways, for example, collecting statistics on the number of individuals who visit our site or when a particular web page is viewed. The information we collect may include some limited personal information, and web beacons allow us to recognize users by accessing cookies. We may also combine the information that we collect through web beacons with other personal information we have collected from you. We use all of this information to personalise and provide a better experience on our website for you. By using our website and our service you consent to these uses of web beacons.
  * ### Password security

When you log in to your Borderlinx account, other users will not be able to access your information, even if they know your account number, without your password. To prevent other people from accessing your information, you should keep your password confidential and secure and be sure to sign off from your web session if you are using a shared computer or mobile device. You can change your password by logging in to 'My Account,' and we recommend that you do change it periodically.
  * ### Credit card information

As a general rule, we do not store credit card information except for customers in certain countries where Borderlinx service is provided in cooperation with a partner. For those countries, customers' credit card information is stored securely in compliance with the credit card industry PCI-DSS security requirements. 
    * For customers in most countries, credit card information is taken and processed on our behalf by the secure servers of Adyen Enterprise Payment Services, a Netherlands Internet Payment Service Provider certified by the major credit card companies. Through Adyen, we fully support the 3D Secure authentication mechanism (referred to by the major credit card companies as 'Verified by Visa' or 'MasterCard SecureCode'). Adyen may need to transfer some information outside the EU area for the purposes of credit card validation and authentication. For more information on Adyen, please [**click here**](http://www.adyen.com/).
    * We also accept payments via PayPal and fully comply with all related security requirements. We do not store any of your PayPal data.
  * ### Shipment information

Information about the packages being shipped to you will be provided to the necessary authorities for export, import, duty and tax purposes, and for security screening. The information may include your name, delivery address, description of the goods, their value, the number of pieces, and the weight of the package. This information is required by law and regulations applicable in the countries from where and to where packages are transported.
  * ### Your e-mail address

We use your e-mail address to communicate with you about your orders (e.g., receipt of packages at your Suite address, questions about the products you have ordered or their value, obtaining your shipping instructions, confirming your orders, reminders about our storage services, and advising you when your package has shipped). We also use your e-mail address to send you communications about our products and services that you request. When you create a Borderlinx account, we ask you if you would like to subscribe to our e-mail newsletter (ezine). Only if you check 'yes' will we send you the newsletter. You can also subscribe to the Borderlinx blog. You may opt out of your newsletter or blog subscription at any time by clicking the link at the bottom of the e-mail. Occasionally we may communicate with you by e-mail to request you to participate in a customer survey. We may also communicate with you via your Twitter account or your account in other social networks, if you sign up to receive such communications.
  * ### Disclosures required by law

We may need to disclose your personal information if required to do so by a court or government agency, or as may otherwise be required by law.

## Websites linked to our site

If you click on any of the external websites linked to the Borderlinx site, the business operating the other site will know that you accessed it from our site. Most of the external links on our site lead you to Merchants who sell the products you are interested in. If you click on a Merchant's site from our site, that Merchant will know the activities and transactions you undertook on that site. External sites may collect personally identifiable information about you. This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of those other websites. You should check their privacy policies if you have concerns about the information they collect.

## Where personal information is stored and processed

  * To enable us to provide Borderlinx services to you, it is necessary to store and process your personal information on our systems and the systems of our trusted partners and suppliers, which are located in Belgium, the United States, and other countries. As stated in our **Terms and Conditions**, by creating a Borderlinx account and using Borderlinx services, you are giving consent for the personal data you submit to be stored and processed in one or more of these locations.

## Your rights

  * You can update or correct your personal details at any time by logging in to 'My Account'. You can request us to remove your personal information by terminating your account or contacting **Customer Service**. However, please note that we may need to keep some personal data in order to process your orders or to comply with our service obligations.
  * We will also provide you, on request a copy of any personal information we hold about you.

## Terms and conditions

Please refer to our Terms and Conditions for additional important information on your use of this website and of Borderlinx services.

Borderlinx Privacy Policy

Updated 17 August 2011

This Privacy Policy is Copyright © 2006-2011 Borderlinx Europe SA. All Rights Reserved.

Revolutionize your shopping experience with Borderlinx package forwarding and international shipping services. With Borderlinx, you have the freedom to shop from your favorite US & EU brands (including buying like a local in the UK, France, Italy, Spain and Germany) and have your items shipped to you globally. Simply register to instantly receive your international US and UK shipping address to start shopping today. Have questions? Learn more about how to shop and ship globally. We ship to 47 countries, including Australia, Egypt, Germany, Kuwait, Malaysia, Saudi Arabia, Singapore, Qatar and UAE.
